Guide to the University of Chicago Library. John Crerar Library. Records 1977-2009
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: John Crerar Library Construction
  - Construction – Reports – A & H Flood Engineering – April, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Reports – A & H Flood Engineering – May to June, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Reports – A & H Flood Engineering – June to July, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Reports – A & H Flood Engineering – August to November, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Reports – A & H Flood Engineering – December, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Reports – A & H Flood Engineering – January to July, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Reports – Hugh Stubbins & Associates, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Reports – Loebl Schlossman & Hackl, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Reports – Superintendents Daily Logs – November to December, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Reports – Superintendents Daily Logs – January to June, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Reports – Superintendents Daily Logs – July to December, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Reports – Superintendents Daily Logs – March to April, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Reports – Field Notebooks, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Reports – Cement Mill Tests, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Reports – Construction Review Notes, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Reports – Settlement Damage Report, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Scheduling – Correspondence and Memos, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Scheduling – Building Schedule, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Scheduling – Hardware Schedule, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Construction – Scheduling – Schedule B's – Dewatering System, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Scheduling – General Notes Listing, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Sketches – "As Builts", 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Sketches – Building Components, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Sketches – Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Structural Calculations, 1983 [1/2] (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Structural Calculations, 1983 [2/2] (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Insurance Rider and Site Observations, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Permits, Certificates and Warranties, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Construction – City of Chicago Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Specification Correspondence, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Construction – Shop Drawing Transmittals, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Construction – Site Utilities, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Construction – List of Construction Documents, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Series II: Missing Books Information
  - Crerar Library Book Plate, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Index Card Copies – Temporary Cards, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Index Card Copies – Accession Number Cards, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Index Card Copies – Missing Book Copies, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Index Card Copies – Atlas or Map Text Volumes, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Index Card Copies – Post 1900 Rare Books, 1983 [1/3] (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Index Card Copies – Post 1900 Rare Books, 1983 [1/3] (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Index Card Copies – Post 1900 Rare Books, 1983 [1/3] (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Index Card Copies – On Indefinite Loan to the Field Museum, c.1983 [1/4] (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Index Card Copies – On Indefinite Loan to the Field Museum, c.1983 [2/4] Folder 3: Index Card Copies – On Indefinite Loan to the Field Museum, c.1983 [3/4] (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Index Card Copies – On Indefinite Loan to the Field Museum, c.1983 [4/4] (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Index Card Copies – On Indefinite Loan to the Prentice Women's Hospital, c. 1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Index Card Copies – ICJ General Stacks, c.1983 [1/2] (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Index Card Copies – ICJ General Stacks, c.1983 [2/2] (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Missing Books – Correspondence and Book List, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Missing Books – List of Putnam Books, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Missing Books – Abernethy, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Missing Books – Accademia del Cimento, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Missing Books – Adams, James, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Missing Books – Adams, John, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Missing Books – Ahlfeld, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Missing Books – Albertus, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Missing Books – Albinus, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Missing Books – Albucassis, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Missing Books – Aldrovandi, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Missing Books – Alpino, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Missing Books – Anathomia, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Missing Books – Andrews, Edmund, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Missing Books – Andrews, Henry, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Missing Books – Apianus, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Missing Books – Appert, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Missing Books – Archimedis, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Missing Books – Argellata,1983 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Missing Books – Aristotle, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Missing Books – Articella, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Missing Books – Aselli, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Missing Books – Ashton, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Missing Books – Astruc, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Missing Books – Aubert, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Missing Books – Augustis, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Missing Books – Aurelianus, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Missing Books – Ausonius, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Missing Books – Averroes, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Missing Books – Avienus, Aratus & Serenus, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Missing Books – Bacci, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Missing Books – Back, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Missing Books – Bacon, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Missing Books – Bagellardi, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Missing Books – Bairo, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Missing Books – Banks, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Missing Books – Barra, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Missing Books – Barclay, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Missing Books – Bartholin, Albert, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Missing Books – Bartholin, Caspar, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Missing Books – Bartholin, Thomas, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Missing Books – Barton, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Missing Books – Bauhin, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Missing Books – Bayer, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Missing Books – Beauties Treasury, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Missing Books – Beccaria, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Missing Books – Bell, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Missing Books – Bellini, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Missing Books – Belt Railway Manuscripts, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Missing Books – Besson, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Missing Books – Benzi, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Missing Books – Berengario, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Missing Books – Berretino, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Missing Books – Bernard, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Missing Books – Bertin, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Missing Books – Beverwijck, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Missing Books – Bewick, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Missing Books – Beyle, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Missing Books – Biringuccio, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Missing Books – Blebelius, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Missing Books – Bock, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Missing Books – Bohn, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Missing Books – Boltz, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Missing Books – Bombelli, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Missing Books – Bonomo, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Missing Books – Borel, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Missing Books – Bossel, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Missing Books – Bohun, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Missing Books – Botalli, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Missing Books – Bowles, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Missing Books – Boyle, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Missing Books – Bradley, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Missing Books – Brahe, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Missing Books – Brandis, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Missing Books – Brasavola, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Missing Books – Brisbane, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Missing Books – Brissot, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Missing Books – Browne, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Missing Books – Bruel, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Missing Books – Brumund, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Missing Books – Bruun, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Missing Books – Buffon, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Missing Books – Bunbury, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Missing Books – Buteo, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Missing Books – Cabei, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Missing Books – Cardano, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Missing Books – Carrarino, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Missing Books – Casati, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Missing Books – Cathell, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Missing Books – Celcus, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Missing Books – Ceredi, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Missing Books – Chapman, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Missing Books – Cheselden, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Missing Books – Chicago Botanical Gardens Report, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Missing Books – Chicago St. Paul Railway Report, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Missing Books – Copernicus, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Missing Books – Chi chung, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Missing Books – Clarisse, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Missing Books – Clavius, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Missing Books – Codronchi, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Missing Books – Colbatch, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Missing Books – Coleman, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Missing Books – Colombani, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Missing Books – Connor, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Missing Books – Cooper, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Missing Books – Cordus, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Missing Books – Cowell, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Missing Books – Crookes, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Missing Books – Cumings, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Missing Books – Cuneo, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Missing Books – Da Costa, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Missing Books – Darwin, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Missing Books – Davis, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Missing Books – Dawplucker, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Missing Books – Descartes, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Missing Books – Decore, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Missing Books – Dee, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Missing Books – De Oculo Tractatio, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Missing Books – Derham, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Missing Books – Deutsche Zeitschrift, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Missing Books – Dictionary, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Missing Books – Donato, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Missing Books – Doppelmayr, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Missing Books – Dorsey, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Missing Books – Douglas, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Missing Books – Durante, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Missing Books – Durer, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Missing Books – Eastern Railroad Company, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Missing Books – Edison, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Missing Books – Edwards, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Missing Books – Elgin, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Missing Books – Erasmus, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Missing Books – Ercker, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Missing Books – Euclid, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Missing Books – Eustachi, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Missing Books – Ewald, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Missing Books – Falconer, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Missing Books – Falleriola, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Missing Books – Falloppio, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Missing Books – Faure, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Missing Books – Fayrer, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Missing Books – Faust, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Missing Books – Filehne, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Missing Books – Fite, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Missing Books – Fontana, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Missing Books – Foy, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Missing Books – Fracastoro, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Missing Books – Freind, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Missing Books – Freud, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Missing Books – Fuller, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Missing Books – Gale, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Missing Books – Galerie, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Missing Books – Galenus, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Missing Books – Galileo, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Missing Books – Gallus, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Missing Books – Galton, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Missing Books – Gardiner, Edmund, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Missing Books – Gardiner, John, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Missing Books – Gauger, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Missing Books – Gauss, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Missing Books – Genger, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Missing Books – Geoffrey Sainte Hilaire, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Missing Books – Geoffroy, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Missing Books – Gibson, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Missing Books – Gilbert, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Missing Books – Glaureanus, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Missing Books – Glauber, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Missing Books – Goddard, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Missing Books – Gourraigne, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Missing Books – Gram, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Missing Books – Granville, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Missing Books – Greverus, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Missing Books – Guillimeau, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Missing Books – Gunsaulus, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Missing Books – Guyot, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Missing Books – Haklyur, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Missing Books – Haller, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Missing Books – Haly abbas, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Missing Books – Hamilton, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Missing Books – Hantzscel, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Missing Books – Harris, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Missing Books – Hartmann, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Missing Books – Harvey, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Missing Books – Heidelberg, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Missing Books – Helmholtz, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Missing Books – Hennin, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Missing Books – Herlicius, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Missing Books – Herschel, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Missing Books – Hery, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Missing Books – Hessus, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Missing Books – Hevelius, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Missing Books – Hewson, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Missing Books – Hierocles, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Missing Books – Highmore, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Missing Books – Hill, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Missing Books – Hippocrates, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Missing Books – Hirst, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Missing Books – Hobbes, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Missing Books – Hoffmann, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Missing Books – Hogelande, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Missing Books – Holmgren, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Missing Books – Hoofnail, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Missing Books – Hooke, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Missing Books – Houbraken, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Missing Books – Houllier, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Missing Books – Howship, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Missing Books – Hua, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Missing Books – Huffaker, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Missing Books – Huish, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Missing Books – Huygens, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Missing Books – Ingenhousz, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Missing Books – International Medical Congress, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Missing Books – Itard, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Missing Books – Japanese Book of Flowers, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Missing Books – Jeffries, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Missing Books – Jena Universitat, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Missing Books – Jennings, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Missing Books – Jewell, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Missing Books – Joachim, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Missing Books – Jocher, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Missing Books – Journal der Pracktischen, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Missing Books – Jovius, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Missing Books – Jurgensen, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Missing Books – Kepler, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Missing Books – Kerr, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Missing Books – Ketelaer, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Missing Books – Khunrath, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Missing Books – Killian, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Missing Books – Kircher, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Missing Books – Kirkpatrick, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Missing Books – Konig, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Missing Books – Kratzenstein, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Missing Books – Kunmo Zui, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Missing Books – Labberton, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Missing Books – Laborie, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Missing Books – Lacepiera, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Missing Books – La Condamine, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Missing Books – Ladimal, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Missing Books – Laennec, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Missing Books – Lamarck, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Missing Books – Laperouse, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Missing Books – Laurentius, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Missing Books – Ledermuller, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Missing Books – Le Gallois, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Missing Books – Leyden, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Missing Books – Lancilotti, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Missing Books – Landois, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Missing Books – La Varenne, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Missing Books – Leonardo, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Missing Books – L'Hopital, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Missing Books – Liber de Morbo, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Missing Books – Liebig, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Missing Books – Lincke, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Missing Books – Linden, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Missing Books – Locke, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Missing Books – Loew von Erlsfeld, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Missing Books – Lommen, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Missing Books – London, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Missing Books – Longfellow, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Missing Books – Lonigo, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Missing Books – Ludwig, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Missing Books – Lull, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Missing Books – Lune, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Missing Books – MacMichael, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Missing Books – Maisonneuve, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Missing Books – Malpighi, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Missing Books – Manarlo, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Missing Books – Manget, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Missing Books – Markham, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Missing Books – Marsigli, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Missing Books – Martin, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Missing Books – Martini, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Missing Books – Mascagni, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Missing Books – Math Manual, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Missing Books – Meares, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Missing Books – Medical Prescriptions, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Missing Books – Medical Times, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Missing Books – Meissner, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Missing Books – Mela, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Missing Books – Meletius, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Missing Books – Mellish, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Missing Books – Memphis, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Missing Books – Mercati, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Missing Books – Mercuriale, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Missing Books – Meyer, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Missing Books – Mitani, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Missing Books – Morgagni, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Missing Books – Moderne, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Missing Books – Monro, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Missing Books – Monte, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Missing Books – Moorland, Joseph, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Missing Books – Moorland, Samuel, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Missing Books – Morton, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Missing Books – Mowrer, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Missing Books – Mulgrave, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Missing Books – Muller, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Missing Books – Mueller, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Missing Books – Myritius, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Missing Books – Napier, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Missing Books – Nave, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Missing Books – Neale, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Missing Books – Nelson, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Missing Books – Newton, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Missing Books – Nicolaus de Cusa, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Missing Books – Nordlinger, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Missing Books – Observations, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Missing Books – Olivieri, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Missing Books – Oribasius, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Missing Books – Oursel, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Missing Books – Papa, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Missing Books – Papin, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Missing Books – Institut de France, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Missing Books – Pasteur, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Missing Books – Pecham, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Missing Books – Peubarch, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Missing Books – Pineau, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Missing Books – Pius II, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Missing Books – Plat, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Missing Books – Plato, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Missing Books – Platina, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Missing Books – Plemp, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Missing Books – Pohl, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Missing Books – Pointer, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Missing Books – Pomodoro, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Missing Books – Poracacchi, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Missing Books – Porta, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Missing Books – Portal, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Missing Books – Pontoppidan, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Missing Books – Proclus, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Missing Books – Ptolemy, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Missing Books – Pye, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Missing Books – Pylander, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Missing Books – Raleigh, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Missing Books – Ramazzini, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Missing Books – Ramelli, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Missing Books – Redi, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Missing Books – Reynolds, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Missing Books – Ricettario, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Missing Books – Roch, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Missing Books – Romoli, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Missing Books – Rosslin, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - Missing Books – Ruscelli, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - Missing Books – Rush, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Missing Books – Ruskin, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Missing Books – Ruysch, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - Missing Books – Ryff, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - Missing Books – Sacro bosco, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Missing Books – Saint Julien, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Missing Books – Sang, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Missing Books – Santorio, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Missing Books – Sappey, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Missing Books – Scappi, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Missing Books – Scarpa, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Missing Books – Scheiner, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Missing Books – Schellig, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Missing Books – Schramm, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Missing Books – Schroter, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Missing Books – Schutte, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Missing Books – Scott, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Missing Books – Scriptores de Rustica, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Missing Books – Senn, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 15)